SmartMaint — L.C PROD. A GMAO for a Moroccan edible-oil plant.
Real-time sync across 27 tables. Offline French voice dictation.
Arabic RTL for the shop floor. Windows installer with auto-update.
Full-stack Next.js and Supabase. Let me show you.
The admin cockpit — every KPI live-computed from intervention history.
Every machine has a QR code, a criticality score, and a full audit trail.
Interventions are Kanban — click and drag to reassign or close.
All 27 tables sync in real time — ~180 ms across all logged-in sessions.
The technician view is mobile-friendly, meant for a tablet on the shop floor.
Every text field has a microphone — Whisper-small, 240 MB, running in the browser.
So the technician can dictate their report in French even offline.
Photos tag automatically as "before" or "after".
And a QR scanner jumps straight to the machine card. Instant identification.
The operator interface is Arabic, right-to-left, kiosk-first.
Giant tactile buttons for panic, quality defect, and requesting EPI.
No training required — an operator filed their first report in under 20 s.
Every request lands instantly on the admin's screen.
And the piece I'm most proud of technically — auto-update, on Windows.
Getting this to work was a two-week deep dive.
The launcher wraps Node in a Windows Job Object with KILL_ON_JOB_CLOSE.
That normally kills every child process when the launcher exits —
so my restart script kept dying with its parent.
Fix: ask WMI to spawn PowerShell — the child ends up outside the Job.
55,000 lines of TypeScript. 80 user stories. 15 sprints.
Three roles, three languages, one platform.
Full source, architecture doc, and blog write-ups are on GitHub.
Live demo in the description. My LinkedIn is on screen.
If you're hiring a full-stack engineer for industrial software, DM me.
Thanks for watching.